<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Recent Content on Androcetus </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://androcetus.com/index.xml</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Sun, 19 Oct 2014 15:44:48 PDT</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>about androcetus</title>
      <link>http://androcetus.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2014 15:44:48 PDT</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://androcetus.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;about androcetus&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Androcetus is a scratchpad of thoughts about topics such as work, success, relationships &amp;amp; life viewed through a lense of masculinity and where possible, femininity.
I&amp;rsquo;ll make the same caveat that &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/Way-Superior-Man-Spiritual-Challenges-ebook/dp/B004A8ZWM4&#34;&gt;David Deida&lt;/a&gt; makes which is that
we are not talking about the behavior and thougths of the biological &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sex&#34;&gt;sexes&lt;/a&gt; of males or females (boy parts, girl parts, or both in some cases).
However, we are discussing the Yin and Yang of &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gender&#34;&gt;gender&lt;/a&gt; that we call masculine and feminine.
Meaning that a woman (girl parts) can behave in masculine ways and a man (boy parts) can behave in feminine ways.
The site takes the bias that men and women will generally improve the quality of their life if they know the difference between masculinity and femininity
AND are able to use this information to choose how to live life more consistent with their personal biology.  Which is to say I believe that:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Men and Women are Equal (in rights) and Different (in behavior)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The general bias of the site is that biological men will have a more fulfilling life if lived mostly in the masculine and that biological women will have a happier life if lived mostly in the feminine.
(Notice the choice of words used for each sex (fulfillment vs happiness).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reason I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to write about this is because for much of my life, I had no idea what it meant to be masculine or feminine. That even
identifiying something as such was &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; and somehow against women&amp;rsquo;s rights. My life dramatically improved once I started learning about the difference between
these two sides of the same coin and I hope to provide something will contribute to other&amp;rsquo;s lives as well.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>